[upbeat rhythmic music]
♪ Come on ♪
♪ Does she walk ♪
♪ Does she talk ♪
♪ Does she come complete ♪
♪ My homeroom, homeroom angel ♪
♪ Always pulled
me from my seat ♪
♪ She was pure like snowflakes ♪
♪ No one could ever stain ♪
♪ The memory of my angel ♪
♪ Could never cause me pain ♪
♪ Years go by I'm lookin'
through a girly magazine ♪
♪ And there's my homeroom
angel on the pages in-between ♪
♪ My blood runs cold ♪
♪ My memory has just been sold ♪
♪ My angel is the centerfold ♪
♪ Angel is the centerfold ♪
♪ My blood runs cold ♪
♪ My memory has just been sold ♪
♪ Angel is the centerfold ♪
♪ Slipped me notes
under the desk ♪
♪ While I was thinkin'
about her dress ♪
♪ I was shy I turned away ♪
♪ Before she caught my eye ♪
♪ I was shakin' in my shoes ♪
♪ Whenever she flashed
those baby-blues ♪
♪ Something had a hold on me ♪
♪ When angel passed close by ♪
♪ Those soft and
fuzzy sweaters ♪
♪ Too magical to touch ♪
♪ To see her in that negligee ♪
♪ Is really just too much ♪
♪ My blood runs cold ♪
♪ Yeah, my memory
has just been sold ♪
♪ My angel is the centerfold ♪
♪ Angel is the centerfold ♪
♪ My blood runs cold ♪
♪ My memory has just been sold ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
♪ Angel is the centerfold ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na-na-na ♪
♪ Na-na-na, na-na-na-na ♪
♪ It's okay I understand ♪
♪ This ain't no
never-neverland ♪
♪ I hope that when
this issue's gone ♪
♪ I'll see you when
your clothes are on ♪
♪ Take your car, yes we will ♪
♪ We'll take your
car and drive it ♪
♪ We'll take it
to a motel room ♪
♪ And take 'em off in private ♪
♪ A part of me has
just been ripped ♪
♪ The pages from my
mind are stripped ♪
♪ Oh no, I can't deny it ♪
♪ Oh yeah, I guess
I gotta buy it ♪
♪ My blood runs cold ♪
♪ My memory has just been sold ♪
♪ My angel is the centerfold ♪
♪ Angel is the centerfold ♪
♪ My blood runs cold ♪
♪ My memory has just been sold ♪
♪ My Angel in the centerfold ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na-na-na ♪
♪ Na-na-na, na-na-na-na ♪
♪ Alright, alright ♪
♪ One, two, three, four ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na-na-na ♪
♪ Na-na-na, na-na-na-na ♪
♪ My blood runs cold ♪
♪ My memory has just been sold ♪
♪ My angel is the centerfold ♪
♪ Angel is the centerfold ♪
♪ My blood runs cold oh yeah ♪
♪ My memory has just been sold ♪
♪ Angel is the centerfold ♪
♪ Na-na, na-na-na-na ♪
♪ Na-na-na, na-na-na-na ♪
♪♪♪